TODOS for Friday 20/11 :
	•	Antonis
        ◦	Create GitHub Repository, in order for everyone to use only GitHub(helps Nick and the rest).
        ◦	Fix bugs on script for splitting review data.
        ◦	Discuss with Adisorn if it is good idea(& feasible with the time we have) to setup VM(Azure).
            ▪	Check how do we add SSH.
            ▪	Install Libs needed for Python and project in general.
            ▪	Python 2.7
            ▪	SciPy
            ▪	Deployment 
            ▪	Email Ramine about Azure. Should we use it?
	•	Adisorn
        ◦	Have the talk with Antonis for VM.
        ◦	Decide which NLP library we will use
            ▪	Research with Hujiang NLP programs(Alchemy | OpenCalais | DBPedia | Gate)
            ▪	Send email to Seyi(Prof. Feyisetan O.O.)  with Hujiang. Ask about NLP tools. | oof1v13@soton.ac.uk
	•	Hujiang
        ◦	See above(speak with Adisorn).
        ◦	Initial commit when the repository is ready. Update the Readme with the Abstract idea of the project or create "Notes" folder in the project and add it there.
	•	Nick 
	    ◦	Create the repository if Antonis doesn't have access by next Wednesday.
	•	Nicola
	    ◦	Call me(Antonis) today afternoon and discuss ToDos.
	•	Everyone: 
	    ◦	Create education account on GitHub -- https://education.github.com/. It gives you access to create 5 private repos.

NEXT MEETING: 
	•	Friday : 20/11/2015 - 3 pm - Hartley Library
